Jamie Unrau

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

jamie@unrau.me

http://unrau.me

778-772-0804

About

I write the words that manifest realms... I send photons of my devising into your eyeballs...

I specialize in reponsive front-end web development, empowered by a background in graphic design, and experience with full-stack MVC frameworks.

Skills

Python C# PHP Swift
Ruby on Rails Wordpress .NET
Javascript Coffeescript Vii2
HTML ERB, HAML
CSS LESS, SCSS, SASS

Photoshop Vim
Illustrator Bash
Pivotal Tracker Netbeans
Git, GitHub Xcode
Subversion Jira

Education

CDI College - 2006

Web Development Certificate

Canmore Collegiate High School - 2003

High School Diploma

Introduction to Interactive
Programming in Python
Coursera.org
Cortificate of Completion
with Distinction

Work Experience

Web Developer

Project House Boutique Business Solutions Inc.

August 2016 - Current

Wordpress Theming - PHP - Javascript - HTML - SASS

At Project House, I meet with clients to discuss their website needs, work with our graphic designers to ensure the responsiveness of designs, and develop new websites for clients, mostly on the Wordpress platform. I also created a custom boilerplate Wordpress theme for us to use in the development of new websites.

Web Development Consultant StemCell Technologies

May 2016 - July 2016

Python - Selenium - QA

I was brought on as a temporary consultant to assist in the launch of the new website. I migrated databases, wrote scripts in Python to automate various tasks, implemented a Selenium test suite to automate QA tasks, and helped deploy the new site to production.

Software Engineer

ReCollect Systems Inc.

June 2014 - Sept 2015

Custom MVC PERL Stack - Xamarin - C# - Coffeescript - HTML - LESS

At ReCollect, I created new features and diagnosed & fixed bugs for their SaaS full-stack web application and their iOS & Android apps. I also created design standards for their apps, as well as a suite of photoshop templates that enabled their customers and contractors to create artwork that complied with those standards.

Volunteer Experience

Volunteer Mentor Ladies Learning Code

Nov 2013 - Current

With Ladies Learning Code, I train students in the basics of various programming languages and development frameworks, including Javascript, Python, and HTML & CSS.